In 1980's Brooklyn, The Most Dangerous Gangsters Were New York City Cops.
The Seven Five is a documentary film directed by Tiller Russell.
Meet the dirtiest cop in NYC history.
Michael Dowd stole money and dealt drugs while
patrolling the streets of '80s Brooklyn.
Himself, played by Michael Dowd.
The Seven Five, also known as Seven Five Precinct, is a 2014 documentary directed by Tiller
Russell, and produced by Eli Holzman, Aaron Saidman, and Sheldon Yellen.
The film looks at police corruption in the 75th Precinct of the
New York Police Department during the 1980s.
The documentary focuses on Michael Dowd and Kenneth Eurell, both corrupt New York City police officers, who were
arrested in 1992, leading to one of the largest police corruption scandals in New York City history.
The documentary uses footage from the Mollen Commission investigation in 1992 and also
provides in-depth commentary from Dowd, Ken Eurell, and Adam Diaz, among others.
The documentary premiered at DOC NYC November 14, 2014.
The film explores themes of new york city,
corruption, mobster, mafia, police corruption.